Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Leo Deaner collection 1902-2006 IBT0022
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Leo Deaner Collection
1902-2008
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0022
50.25 Linear Feet
This collection contains correspondence, memorandums, conference materials, notes, chapters from novels, pieces of news, obituaries, and photographs relating to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters amassed by member Leo Deaner. The materials date from 1902 to 2006.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into eighteen subject series: James R. Hoffa, Teamsters History, Teamsters Leaders, Contracts and Agreements, Project RISE, Personal/Family Files, Pennsylvania Local Unions, Conventions, Local Union Trusteeships, Yager-Kaiser Hearings, John Morris/Local 115, Lyndon LaRouche, Hamilton Trial Transcripts, Ron Carey Investigation, Miscellaneous Research Files, Notes and Subject Binders, and James P. Hoffa.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, memorandums, conference materials, notes, chapters from novels, pieces of news, obituaries, and photographs relating to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters amassed by member Leo Deaner. The materials date from 1902 to 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Leo Deaner, 2008-2010 [2008.065, 2008.075, 2008.078, 2009.083]
Labor unions; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America.; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
- James R. Hoffa Materials, 1944-2004; Series 1; 2 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  The materials of this series include correspondence, memorandums, conference materials, notes, chapters from novels, pieces of news, and photographs. They range in date from 1994 to 2004, and represent the life and disappearance of James R. Hoffa. The series is maintained the order in which it was received; the beginning of the series is chronological, followed by photographs of Hoffa in various places.
  Arrangement
  Arranged in the order it was recieved: chronologically followed by photographs and noted by subject
  - Hoffa Drive Decal, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - National Highway Safety Act, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hoffa - Civil Rights, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Name is Hoffa, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hoffa - Freight Organizing, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fight For Me - Hoffa, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Drive - Jo Hoffa, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy, 1950; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Time, 1957; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Newsweek, 1958; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hoffa-Canada, 1958; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 89, 1958; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - TIME Magazine, 1959; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hoffa 1961, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Deaner-Delegate Cred. IBT Convention, 1961; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dom Abata (777), 1964; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Local 124 - Steel Workers, 31 January 1984; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Partin - 5, 1963, November 2005; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Holmes - 337, 1 November 1987, 3 August 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hoffa and Local 239, 1961; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Hoffa - 1961 IB Convention, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - The Hoodlums Behind Hoffa Argosy, 1961; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Hoffa Studies on the Left, 1962; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 1962/2002 Nashville Trial, 3-4 April 2002; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Hoffa 1963, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Hoffa 1963, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Hoffa - NMFA, 1964; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Man's, June 1964; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Hoffa Trial, 1964; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Hoffa Autograph - IBT Convention, 1966; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Argosy, 1969; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Free Hoffa Bumber Stickers, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Hoffa Doublecross, 1970; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hoffa-Partin, 1971; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Hoffa - One Of A Kind, 1971; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Hoffa 1972, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Hoffa 1973, Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Organized Crime Behind Nixon, 1974; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Overdrive Magazine, 1975; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Hoffa Playboy, 1975; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Action For Hoffa - JC 42, 1975; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Hoffa 1976, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Hoffa 1978, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Hoffa - Tony Pro, 1978; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hoffa Playboy, 1978; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hoffa 1980, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hoffa 1982, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Hoffa 1985, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Hoffa-Franco, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hoffa 1989, Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Hoffa 1991, series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Hoffa - Ragano, 1992; series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Hoffa 1992, series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hoffa-Frankos, 1992; series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Hoffa movie Press Kit, 1992; series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Hoffa The Movie, 1992; series 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Hoffa 1993, series 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Phila. - Allen, 1993; series 1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Hoffa 1994/95, 1994-1995; series 1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Hoffa-Sheeran, 1995; series 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Local 326/Frank Sheeran, 1995; series 1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Hoffa 1996, series 1 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Hoffa - Detroit Sunday Journal, 1997; series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hoffa 1997, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Hoffa - Labor Hall Of Fame, 1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa 1999-2001, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Partin/Hoffa, 1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hoffa - New Labor Forum, 1999; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Death - A. Giacalone, 2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hoffa DNA, 2001-2002; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hoffa - out of the Jungle, 2001; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hoffa 2002, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hoffa 2003, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sheeram Book, 2004; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hoffa 2004, February 2004; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Detroit, 1996,1998,2000; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - McClellan committee Second Interim Report James R Hoffa, 5 August 1959; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Out Of The Jungle - Thaddius Nathan Russell, 2000; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Hoffa In chattanooga, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hoffa and Maritime Leaders, 1959; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa in Philadelphia, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hoffa Pictures, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hoffa in NJ, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Hoffa/Beck Picture, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hoffa/English Picture, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - FBI Special Report, 2002; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Hoffa-Kennedy, 1959; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Hoffa and English, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Hoffa Visits Israel - Daughter Barbara, Golda, and Jimmy, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Hoffa and Presser, undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Hoffa Convicted, 1964; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Hoffa/Cobo Hall, 1966; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Hoffa in St. Louis, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Photo of Hoffa and Wife, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hoffa and McCarthy, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Hoffa and Grandaughter Barbra Jo Crancer, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Hoffa and Son, 1944,1962; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - The Jimmy Hoffa I knew - David W. Salmon, 1995; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Recollections By David W. Salmon - Part Six: I joined Teamsters Local 688, 2004; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Recollections By David W. Salmon - Part Seven: My Advanced Education, 1953-1968; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Recollections By David W. Salmon - Part Eight: Golden Handcuffs, 1968-1978; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - James R. Hoffa Inducted into the Labor Hall of Fame, 1999; Series 1 (Box 165, Folder 2)
- Teamsters History, 1902-2006; Series 2; 4.5 Linear Feet
  The materials of this series include correspondence, memorandums, conference materials, notes, chapters from novels, and pieces of news. They range in date from 1902 to 2006, and represent the history of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. The series maintained the general order in which it was received, and is divided into two subseries: Campaign and Voting Records, and Local 776 Bylaws and Constitutions.
  *See Union Newspapers Collection (LAC0013-Box 11)for newspaper materials from this collection.
  Arranged in the order it was recieved.
  - Local 776 Campaign and Voting Records, 1957-1990; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Local 776 Election Records [1], December 1957; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Local 776 Election Records [2], December 1960; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Local 776 Election Records [3], December 1963-October 1964; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Local 776 Election Records [4], December 1966; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Local 776 Election Records [5], November-December 1969; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Local 776 Election Records [6], August-December 1972; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Local 776 Election Records [7], September-December 1975; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Local 776 Election Records [8], March-December 1978; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Local 776 Election Protest-Charles Deaner Records, October 1978-April 1979; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Local 776 elections: Election Eligibility, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Sample Ballot, December 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Talley and Williams, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Dedicated Teamsters for Action handouts-Local 776 election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Teamsters for Teamster leaflets-Local 776 election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - "Vote for TFT" and "Your Money" Campaign leaflets-Teamsters for Teamsters, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Teamsters for Teamster-poster, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Teamsters for Teamster:Rite Aid, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Teamsters for Teamster UPS, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters for Teamsters-Voting Card, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Local 776 election-VOICE Ticket, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Local 776 election-Rank and File Ticket, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Local 776 election: Bill Still Card, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Local 776 election: Don Harvey, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Local 776 election: Russel East, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Local 776 election: Phil Starner card, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Local 776 election: Warren Brown card, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - TFT's Election issue-Local 776 election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Local 776 election: Campaign Buttons and Memorabilia, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Local 776 elections: VOICE ticket, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Beamer: Local 776 election Issue, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Berkheimer-Local 776 election Issue, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Dale Witmer-Local 776 election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Deaner-Local 776 election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Deaner- Penn Harris: Local 776 election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Don Thomas-Independent ticket-Local 776 Election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Shugart/Foy Ticket-Local 776 election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Louis Scarangella-Local 776 election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Dirt-Shugart-Local 776 election, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Local 776 election: Notes and Correspondence, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Local 776 elections: Voting card and sample ballot, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Nominations-Local 776 elections, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Results-Local 776 elections, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Teamsters for Teamster-Chuck Shughart, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Teamsters for Teamsters-Dirt, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Teamsters for Teamster-Campaign Materials [1], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Teamsters for Teamster-Campaign Materials [2], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Local 776 elections: Ammons Team, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Local 776 elections: Ammons Ticket-Dirt, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Local 776 elections: The Brotherhood Team, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Local 776 elections: The Brotherhood Team-Dirt, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Local 776 elections: independent Candidates, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Local 776 elections: newspapers, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Local 776 elections: Nominations, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Local 776 election: Campaign Buttons and Memorabilia, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Local 776 election: Ballot, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Local 776 election: Results, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Local 776 elections: Dirt, unsigned, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Teamsters for Teamsters-1st Mailing, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Teamsters for Teamsters-2nd Mailing, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Teamsters for Teamster-Handout, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Teamsters-Expenses, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Teamsters for Teamsters-Notes and Correspondence, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Local 776 elections: Andy Kohr ticket, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Local 776 elections: Andy Kohr newsletter, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Local 776 elections: Ron Fike Ticket, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Local 776 elections: Campaign Buttons and Memorabilia, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Local 776 elections: Election Procedures, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Local 776 elections: Election Results, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Local 776 Bylaws and Constitutions, 1946-1985; Series 2 Subseries 2
    This subseries is in chronological order.
    The materials of this subseries includes draft proposals, amendments, and official copies relating the Bylaws and Constitution of Local 776. They range from 1946 to 1985.
    - Current Bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Drive Bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Harrisburg-Milton Bylaws, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Bylaws, Harrisburg, 1946; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Drivers Welfare Association Proposals, 1949-1968; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - IBT-Proposed Model Bylaws, 1971-1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Proposed Bylaws Amendments and Correspondence, 1974; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Proposed Bylaws Amendments and Correspondence, 1977; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Proposed Bylaws Amendments and Correspondence, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Proposed Bylaws Amendments and Correspondence, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Bylaws Proposals, 1991-1993; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Local 776 Events, 1940-1993; Series 2 Subseries 3
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    This subseries encompasses all family gatherings and official public events hosted or sponsored by Local 776. This includes memorials, charity drives, sports tournaments, holiday events, family gatherings, political rallies, banquets, and labor-related workshops ranging from 1940 to 1993. Materials include flyers, news clippings, bulletins, correspondence, personal notes, and photographs.
    - Annual Golf Tournament [1], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Annual Golf Tournament [2], 1988-1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Annual Golf Tournament [3], 1991-1993; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Children's Christmas Party [1], 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Children's Christmas Party and Parade [2], 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Children's Christmas Party [3], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Children's Christmas Party [4], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Children's Christmas Party [5], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Children's Christmas Party [6], 1990-1992; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Commercial Driver's License Testing, 1991-1992; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - DRIVE Dinners, 1991-1993; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Harrisburg Senators-Baseball game, July 17, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Harrisburg Area Community College-Annual Meetings, 1991-1992; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Hazardous Materials and CPR Seminars, April 1988- February 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Hershey Park Trip [1], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Hershey Park Trip [2], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Hershey Park Trip [3], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Jesse Jackson Rally, April, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Labor Day, 1992; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Local 776 Membership Meeting-John Morris Visit, April 13, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Local 776-Little League Photos, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Local 776 Picnic [1], 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Local 776 Picnic [2], 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Local 776 Picnic [3], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Local 776 Picnic [4], 1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Local 776 Picnic [5], 1992-1993; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Local 776 Retiree Club-Party and Visits, 1990-1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Local 776-50th Anniversary, October, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Loca 776-List of Events and Meetings, 1988-1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - List of Retiree Events, 1986-1992; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Local 776 Steward's Visit to IBT Headquarters, Washington D.C., 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Memorial Day Parades and Community Events, 1989-1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters [1], 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters [2], 1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania Conference of Teamsters [3], 1992; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Pennsylvania Labor Communications Association-Biennal Convention, 1992; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Motor Truck Association-3rd Annual Installation Meeting, October 19, 1974; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Penn State Class and Correspondence, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - POW-MIA Veterans Appreciation Day, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Reading Fair, August 1937-September 1942; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Special Convention Nomination, March 16, 1961; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - St. Patrick's Day Parade Photos, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Solidarity Day, 1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Stewards Banquet [1], 1985; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Stewards Banquet [2], 1986; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Stewards Banquet [3], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Stewards Banquet [4], 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Stewards Banquet [5], 1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Stewards Banquet [6], 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Stewards Banquet [7], 1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Stewards Banquet [8], 1992; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Stewards Banquet [9], 1993; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Teamsters Credit Union-Banquet News clippings, 1958; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - 50th Anniversary-Teamsters Federal Credit Union, February-October 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Teamster Leadership Academy, April-July 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Teamsters Organizing School and Steward's Seminar [1], 1987; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Teamsters Organizing School [2], 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Workers Memorial Day [1], April, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Workers Memorial Day [2], April, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Workers Memorial Day [3], April, 1991; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Workers Memorial Day [4], April, 1992; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Workers Memorial Day [5], April, 1993; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - WWII-Teamsters Blood Drive, 1940; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Local 776 Administrative Records, 1940-1998; Series 2 Subseries 4
    This subseries compromises the administrative files, official correspondence, and internal financial records of Local 776 officials, including those of Charles Leo Deaner. It ranges from early 1940 to 1993. Materials include internal and external correspondence of Charles Leo Deaner, his personal notes, Local 776's financial statements, administrative logs, newsclippings, and membership surveys. It also includes historical audio-visual items such as film reels and videocassettes.
    This subseries is arranged chronologically. If marked by a number in brackets, the title's chronological order will reset to the earliest marked date.
    - Local 776 Union Hall-Political Forum, 1940; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Message from James Flaherty, October 6, 1941; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Local 776 and Joint Council 20 Tax Records [1], 1946; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Local 776 and Joint Council 20 Tax Records [2], 1947; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Local 776 and Joint Council 20 Tax Records [3], 1948-1949; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 5)